CHANODOM UTSAHAJIT

CONTACT INFORMATION

079-569-82635 | 074-551-45159

BZKWORK1993@GMAIL.COM

CHANODOM-UTSAHAJIT.COM

FLAT 1 ARGYLE HOUSE 1 DEE ROAD RICHMOND, UK TW9 2JN

SKILLSET

UX / UI DESIGN



SERVICE DESIGN





BUSINESS INNOVATION



FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPMENT

TOOLKITS

VISUAL DESIGN

PHOTOSHOP



ILLUSTRATOR

AFTER EFFECTS



RAPID PROTOTYPING

EXPERIENCE DESIGN





SKETCH INVISION





UNITY 3D





HTML5 + CSS3 + JS



USABILITY TESTING

TOBII EYE TRACKING



MORAE



LANGUAGES

THAI

MOTHER-TONGUE

ENGLISH

JAPANESE

BEGINNER

INTERESTS

VIRTUAL & AUGMENTED REALITY



GAME DEVELOPMENT



TRAVEL & EXPLORATION



EXTREME SPORTS & TRIATHLON

ABOUT ME

I am a graduate in the field of UX design, Business, and Technology with experience and passion for designing and innovating digital experiences using state-of-the-art technology and methodologies. Additionally, my proficiency in visualisation allows me to perform creative tasks, as well as to collaborate and communicate ideas at ease through illustrations and infographics.

EXPERIENCE

VIKER (FEB 2018 - APR 2018) **UX/CREATIVE INTERN**

Involved directly in hypercasual mobile game developments, assisting in user experience design process and graphical assets creation. Created early Unity-based prototypes, UA videos and App Store contents for published games.



KEY

Wireframing &

LEARNINGS

PRECISION PRINTING (OCT 2016 - JAN 2017)

CREATIVE INTERN

In charge of the production of graphical materials for blogs, and the visual redesign of customer artwork guideline documents for the purpose of better comprehension and modernisation.



& Typography

PwC UK (JUN 2016 - AUG 2016) CONSULTING INTERN

Acted as a visual UX designer for 'Startup Journey' project, responsible for potential customer research and analysis, and prototyping which includes UI redesign wireframing and



Research & Media Prototyping

CYBERPRINT GROUP (JUN 2015 - AUG 2015)

CONSULTING INTERN

Assisted in the company's adoption of digital printing. Further led the planning of personalised promotional offerings and print prototyping for Mother's Day and National Book Exhibition Week.



Business Model

CHOMASOFT (JUN 2014 - JAN 2016)

CO-FOUNDER

Acted as a co-project manager for the mobile game development of 'Rubber Dash Story'. Experimented with Scrum to lead the development process. Involved in the UI and gameplay concept ideation process, and minor front-end code edits.



SAMAGGI SAMAGOM (SEP 2013 - JUL 2014) MEDIA CREATOR VOLUNTEER

Responsible for the production of advertisement materials such as posters and videos for charity and public events. Co-produced promotional video for Samaggi Concert feat. LIPTA and social media posters for Samaggi Games 2014.



Team Building & Under Pressure

EDUCATION

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGN (UXD) (2017 - 2018)

KINGSTON UNIVERSITY LONDON

User Research, Customer Journeys & Personas, Wireframing, Rapid Prototyping, Usability Testing, Design Thinking, Digital Studio Practice (++)

INNOVATION, ENTREPRENEURSHIP **& MANAGEMENT (IEM)** (2015 - 2016)

IMPERIAL COLLEGE BUSINESS SCHOOL

Business Economics, Organisational Behavior & HR Management, Project & Strategic Management, Design & Innovation Management, Agile, International Marketing (++)

COMPUTER SCIENCE WITH INTELLIGENT SYSTEMS (2012 - 2015)

KING'S COLLEGE LONDON

Introductory Artificial Intelligent, Introductory Robotics, Computing Foundations, Object-Oriented Programming, Computer Vision (++)



Dissertation: "Service Redesign to transform CyberPrint Group, a Printing Corporate, towards Digital



Dissertation: "How to create launch a Disruptive Innovation from within an





Dissertation: "How Visual Richness in a Virtual Reality Environment affects the Interaction Performance of Users?"